[♪ classical music playing]
[electricity buzzes]
[♪ piano playing]
[snoring]
（科米）
-[chair creaks] -Mmm.
[breathes heavily] Mmm. Hmm.
什么事？
-Oh. -What?
-罗夫？ -什么事？
-Rowlf? -What?
你这段时间都在弹琴吗？
Have you been playing this whole time?
你以为是什么？
Well, what did you think it was?
你脑海中的怀旧集锦吗？
Some kinda sentimental montage in your head?
我们又要表演了，青蛙
-[mutters] -We're doing the show again, frog.
对哦
[gasps] Oh, that's right. Uh…
斯库特，时候到了
Scooter, it's time.
没问题，老大
You got it, boss.
莎宾娜卡本特，30秒后开演，卡本特小姐
Sabrina Carpenter. Thirty seconds to curtain, Ms. Carpenter.
卡本特小姐？
Ms. Carpenter?
谢谢你，斯库特
Thank you, Scooter.
天啊，是你，我好爱你的衣服
Oh, my God. It's you. I love your outfit. [chuckles]
我也是，你得换衣服
So do I. You're gonna have to change.
是，女士
Yes, ma'am.
那是我的假发吗？
Is that my wig?
我不戴假发的，这是我的真发
I don't wear wigs. This is my real hair.
我也一样
Oh. Yeah. Same.
-不，我…我知道 -不，我知道你知道
-No, I… And I know that. -No, I know you know.
-很好 -好
-Great. -Okay.
[trumpet blares]
《大青蛙布偶秀：特别场》
欢迎观赏《大青蛙布偶秀：特别场》 特别嘉宾是莎宾娜卡本特
It's The Muppet Show with our very special guest star, Sabrina Carpenter. [cheers]
[audience cheers]
[♪ "The Muppet Show Theme Song" playing]
该演奏音乐，该点亮灯光
♪ It's time to play the music It's time to light the lights ♪
该见见今晚登场的布偶了
♪ It's time to meet the Muppets On The Muppet Show tonight ♪
该化好妆容，该好好打扮
♪ It's time to put on makeup It's time to dress up right ♪
该揭开今晚《大青蛙布偶秀》的序幕了
♪ It's time to raise the curtain On The Muppet Show tonight ♪
我们干嘛老是来这里？
♪ Why do we always come here? ♪
这个问题大概永远无解
♪ I guess we'll never know ♪
被迫看这场秀
♪ It's like a kind of torture ♪
有点像酷刑
♪To have to watch the show ♪
[music continues]
但现在让我们开演吧
♪ But now let's get things started ♪
你们快开演吧
♪ Why don't you get things started? ♪
该开演了
♪ It's time to get things started ♪
最令人惊叹、鼓舞人心 欢欣喜悦、布偶天成
♪ On the most sensational, inspirational Celebrational, Muppetational ♪
这就是我们的《大青蛙布偶秀》
♪ This is what we call The Muppet Show ♪
[trumpet screeches]
[audience laughs]
[screams]
[audience cheering]
谢谢…谢谢
Thank you. Thank you. [mutters] Uh, thank you. [chuckles]
大家好，欢迎观赏《大青蛙布偶秀》
Hi-ho, and welcome to The Muppet Show, everybody.
[audience cheering]
我们很高兴能回到这个舞台 一切就是从这里开始
You know, we are so excited to be back on the very stage where it all started,
然后结束，然后
and then ended, and then,
可能会再次开始，看今晚表现如何啰
is maybe starting again depending on how tonight goes.
他们居然要重演老戏码
Hmph. I can't believe they're doing the old show again.
好好的何必改
Well, if it ain't broke.
不，他们是好穷，所以才会来表演
No, they are broke. That's why they're doing it.
-[laughs] -[audience laughs]
好，为我们开场的是
Okay. Now to kick us off,
我们的特别来宾
it's our very special guest,
轰动乐坛的创作歌手，世界级的巨星
a sensational singer-songwriter and global superstar,
独一无二的莎宾娜卡本特
-the one and only, Sabrina Carpenter. Yay! -[audience cheers]
[laughing, clamoring]
安静点，一群混混
Ugh. Quiet. [groans] Hooligans.
快点，丢他
Do it. Do it. Toss. [laughs]
[yelps, grunts]
[laughing]
住手，否则赶你们出去
Stop, or you'll be removed.
别担心，山姆，交给我
Don't worry, Sam. I got it.
[♪ "Manchild" playing]
[laughing]
你说手机坏了，其实是忘了充电
♪ You said your phone was broken Just forgot to charge it ♪
你这身行头，天啊，希望你是在搞笑
♪ Whole outfit you're wearing God, I hope it's ironic ♪
你刚说你完事了？ 我都不知道我们开始了
♪ Did you just say you're finished? Didn't know we started ♪
这一切都太熟悉了，宝贝，是什么来着？
♪ It's all just so familiar, baby What do you call it? ♪
-愚蠢 -咕咕
-♪ Stupid ♪ -♪ Cluck-cluck ♪
-还是迟钝？ -咕
-♪ Or is it slow? ♪ -♪ Cluck ♪
-也许是没用？ -咕咕
-♪ Maybe it's useless? ♪ -♪ Cluck-cluck ♪
但有个更可爱的词
♪ But there's a cuter word for it ♪
-咕？ -我知道
-♪ Cluck? ♪ -♪ I know ♪
巨婴男
-♪ Manchild ♪ -[chickens vocalizing]
你为什么总是跑来找我？
♪ Why you always come a-running to me? ♪
我还要过活
♪ It's my life ♪
饶了这个无辜的女人吧
♪ Won't you let an innocent woman be ♪
从没听过“自我照顾”
♪ Never heard of self-care ♪
[yells]
你的脑容量只有一半
♪ Half your brain just ain't there ♪
Whoa.
巨婴男
-♪ Manchild ♪ -[exclaiming]
你为什么总是跑来找我？打消我所有的
♪ Why you always come a-running Taking all my ♪
我喜欢男生搞点欲擒故纵
♪ Oh, I like my boys playing hard to get ♪
也喜欢男人软弱无能
♪ And I like my men all incompetent ♪
我发誓是他们选了我，不是我选了他们
♪ And I swear they choose me I'm not choosing them ♪
-阿们，男人们 -咕咕
-♪ Amen, hey, men ♪ -♪ Cluck-cluck ♪
巨婴男
-♪ Manchild ♪ -[laughing]
你为什么总是跑来找我？
♪ Why you always come a-running to me? ♪
[vocalizing]
我还要过活
[Carpenter] ♪ It's my life ♪
饶了这个无辜的女人吧
♪ Won't you let an innocent woman be? Oh ♪
我喜欢男生搞点欲擒故纵
[singers] ♪ And I like my boys Playing hard to get ♪
也喜欢男人软弱无能
♪ And I like my men all incompetent ♪
[laughs]
[clucking]
阿们，男人们
♪ Amen, hey, men ♪
-[shrieks] -[audience laughs]
-[clucking] -[audience cheering]
真厉害
-Great talent! -Whoo-hoo!
-我喜欢，再来 -对，太棒了
-Love it! More! More! -[chuckles] Yes, it's great.
好令人兴奋的开场，科米叔叔
Wow, what an exciting opening, Uncle Kermit.
做得好，鸡群，风扇的事真的很抱歉
Great job, Chickens. Again, I'm sorry about the fan.
我好羞愧
-[grunting] -[Sam] I'm mortified.
-斯库特，过来 -好
-Scooter. Come here, come here, come here. -Uh. Yeah.
后台怎么这么拥挤？
Why is it so crowded back here?
这些都是表演名单上的人，老大
Well, uh, these are all the acts in the show, boss.
你确定我批准那名单了吗？
What? Are you sure I approved all of that?
还有更多呢
And more.
[whistle blows]
我们快走，该上台了
[Muppet 1] Let's go already. We gotta get on stage.
记得大家多期待参与我们首场回归秀吗？
Remember how excited everyone was to be on our first show back?
你还一直跟他们说 他们的表演听起来很有趣
And you kept telling them that their acts sounded fun.
斯库特，大家都知道“听起来很有趣”
[scoffs] Scooter, everybody knows that "that sounds fun"
是一种委婉拒绝的方式
is just a polite way of saying no.
对，还蛮隐晦的，老大
Yeah, that feels pretty indirect, boss.
这可能会造成问题
-Hmm. -You know, this could be a problem.
好，下一个找我谈的人一定会被删掉
Okay. Well, the next person who talks to me is definitely getting cut.
科米
-Mm-hmm. -Oh, Kermie.
[audience laughs]
[humming]
不好意思，艺人要过
-Excuse moi, talent walking. -Hmm?
哪里有艺人？
[gasps] Oh. Oh, where's the talent?
-我，我就是… -谁？
-Me. Me. I'm the t… [sighs] -Who? [grunts]
科米，重回剧院 为人们送上他们真正想看的
Oh, Kermit. Isn't it wonderful being back in the theater again,
是不是很美妙？
giving the people what they truly want?
也就是我
Moi. [chuckles]
祝你好运
-[sighs] -Good luck.
斯库特？
Scooter? [stutters]
是啊，猪猪，说起来这场秀…有点长
Yeah. Um, Piggy, uh, you know… [chuckles] …the show is, uh, it's running kinda long,
而且你似乎有两场表演
and, uh, you know, it looks like you're doing two acts.
没错，关于音乐表演
Exactly. Now about the musical number,
当我以爱神造型从巨型贝壳中现身
when I emerge from the giant seashell dressed as Aphrodite,
那三百个跳舞的斯巴达人一定要知道
let's make sure our 300 dancing Spartans know to exit the Trojan horse
冲出特洛伊木马的时机就是我的降B高音
precisely on my [singsongy] high B flat.
对，我只是随口提一下
Right. Uh, just thinking out loud here,
但你认为那些精确的历史考据 会抢你的风头吗？
but, uh, you think maybe all that historical accuracy might upstage you?
[laughing] No.
不会
[audience laughs]
科米
-Kermit. Kermit. -[sighs]
我不小心听到了，因为我在偷看你们
I couldn't help but overhear because I was spying on you guys.
我可以帮你删减节目内容
If you need, I can help you trim some of the show.
真的吗？谢了，你有什么想法？
Oh, really? Uh, thanks. What were you thinking?
从头顶剪一些如何？
How about a little off the top?
-Ah? -[chuckles]
道具喜剧现在可能帮不了我们，福滋
I don't know if prop comedy is gonna help us right now, Fozzie.
那我只好戴上我的思考帽了
Oh. Guess I'll have to put on my thinking cap then.
Hmm? [gasps]
-喜欢吗？如何？ -当然
-Ah? Like it? Huh? Huh? Huh? -Uh, you know, sure.
如果它能让你想到删减节目内容的方法
If it can help you think of how to cut some acts from the show.
没问题，我已经有点子了
You got it, pal. Got an idea already.
Oh.
塞斯罗根
Hey, Seth Rogen.
福滋，这太棒了
Oh, hey, Fozzie. This is incredible.
我一直梦想能登上这个舞台
It's always been a dream of mine to be here. [chuckles]
你有其他梦想吗？
Ooh. Got any other dreams?
这是什么意思？
Uh-oh. What does that mean?
你被删掉了
[sighs] You're cut.
什么？删掉？我是执行制作人耶
What? Cut? I'm the executive producer.
那请你通知自己，我们要改变路线了
Then you can let yourself know we're going in a different direction.
[audience laughs]
[audience applauding]
下一位表演者是世界上 最无所畏惧的冒险家兼行为艺术家
Our next act is the world's most fearless daredevil/performance artist,
他多年来都不断撼动观众与保险公司的心
who's been shocking audiences and insurance companies for years.
让我们欢迎伟大的贡佐
Let's hear it for The Great Gonzo.
-[audience cheers] -[trumpets blare]
谢谢，感激不尽
Thank you. Thank you so much.
看啊，是我，伟大的贡佐
Behold, it is I, The Great Gonzo.
今晚我要尝试以自动驾驶的溜冰鞋
And tonight I will attempt this deadly obstacle course
挑战这条致命的障碍赛道
on self-driving roller skates.
同时背出奥斯卡金像奖
All the while reciting every Academy Award winner
所有的最佳女配角奖得主
in the category of Best Supporting Actress.
[♪ "O Fortuna" playing]
[laughs] Whoo-hoo. Ignite the rings.
点燃火圈
放开刀片
Release the blades. [laughs]
表演现在开始
And it starts right now.
歌蒂韩、露琵塔尼咏欧、莎莉温德丝
Goldie Hawn, Lupita Nyong'o, Shelly Winters.
[bangs, clatters]
[audience gasps]
那样真痛苦
Whoo. That was painful.
他痛苦还是我们痛苦？
For him or for us?
都痛苦
-Both. [laughs] -[laughs]
现在请观赏《戴假发的猪》
[announcer] And now, "Pigs in Wigs."
[♪ classical music playing]
美乃滋三明治郡的猪格顿公爵夫人
Duchess Piggerton of County Mayo Upon Sandwich.
[audience laughs]
费料勋爵和…他的女伴
Lord Scrappleton and… his plus one.
什么？
What? [grumbles]
亲爱的
Darling.
多耀眼的晚宴啊，亲爱的
[sighs] What a dazzling soiree, mon chéri.
你好吗？很高兴见到你
Oh. Hello. How are you? Lovely to see you.
她竟然还敢在这里露脸
She has some nerve showing her face around here.
好时髦的装扮 我爱死那个莫名其妙的玩意了
What a chic ensemble. Love whatever that is.
看来今晚的服装规定只是建议而已
Apparently the dress code was optional tonight.
亲爱的，你真是个小恶魔
[laughs] Darling, you're so devilish.
-[laughs] -[laughs]
你能行行好，帮我拿杯饮料吗？拜托
Say, could you be a dear and fetch us a beverage? Pretty please?
当然好，我的小松饼，我马上回来
Oh. Of course, my crumpet. I'll be right back.
-[chuckles] -Mmm. [chuckles]
我的爱人，可以浮上水面了
Oh, lover. The coast is clear.
猪猪
-Psst, Piggy. -Hmm?
我忘了跟你说 我们得重新帮你的爱人选角
I forgot to tell you, we had to recast your lover.
什么？谁啊？
W-What? Wi-With who?
你好啊
Hola.
你们一定是在开玩笑
You've gotta be kidding me.
我跟你一样困惑，好吗？
Hey, I'm just as confused as you are, okay?
好啦，我们继续演吧
[sighs] All right. Let's just get on with it.
[clears throat]
爱人，我是多么想念你那棱角分明的下巴
Oh, lover. How I've missed your chiseled chin,
你那乌黑浓密的秀发 还有强壮有力的臂膀
your luscious, thick head of raven hair, and your big strong arms.
你在跟我说话吗？
You talking to me?
对
Yep.
找到你了，亲爱的
There you are, my darling. Uh…
你是哪位，阁下？
And who are you, kind sir?
我不知道
I don't know.
我本来在后面闲聊 有人却帮我套上这件怪外套
I was back there schmoozing when someone put me in this weird jacket
把我推到台上，好吗？
and threw me on the stage, okay?
糟了，我被逮到了
Oh, no. I've been caught.
这下让我难以抉择的
And now my public lover and my secret lover,
正牌爱人和秘密爱人
whomst I am tornt betweenst,
必须决斗至死 只因他们如此疯狂地爱着我
must duel to the death because they're so madly in love with moi.
对，说到这个 我应该告诉你，我邂逅了一个人
Uh, yes. Uh, about that, I should tell you, I… I've met someone.
什么？什么时候？
What? When?
刚刚在切肉台那边
Just now by the carving station.
我知道才过了几秒钟，但那是真爱
Oh, I know it's only been a few seconds but it's true love.
这是怎么回事？
What is happening here?
你听到他的话了，那是爱情 恭喜你，朋友
You heard him, okay. It's love. Good for you, my friend.
谢谢，我们好幸福哦
-Oh, thank you. We're oh, so happy. -[mutters, scoffs]
算了，我要离开这里，免得把脸丢光
Ugh, forget it. I'm getting out of here while I still have my dignity.
-[sighs] -[audience laughs]
[gasps]
[screams]
[cheering]
两位的投掷物
Your projectiles, sirs.
太迟了，短剧结束了
Uh, too late. Sketch is over.
你还是把它们留下吧，这场秀还很长
Actually, why don't you leave 'em. There's a lot more of this show left.
真是不幸
-Unfortunately. [laughs] -[laughs]
好，羽毛黏好了 等它干了再抱人，下一位
Okay. Feather's glued. Don't hug anyone till it is dry. Next.
好，各位
Okay, everybody.
你们的名字都按明确顺序 列在这份演出流程表上
All of your names are on this run of show in a highly specific order.
只要我手上拿着这份名单
And as long as I have this list in my hands,
这场秀就会顺利进行
the show will go off without a hitch.
奥林匹亚杜卡琪斯、莫妮克
Olympia Dukakis. Mo'Nique.
[crashes]
你这么做好像在挑战命运
Feels like you kinda tempted fate with that one.
[audience laughs, applaud]
[musical fanfare]
好，谢谢各位
Huh. Okay. Uh, thank you very much.
接下来的音乐表演，我们要走上街头
Now, for our next musical number, let's take it to the streets.
鼠患横行的街头
The rat infested streets. Ooh.
[sirens blaring]
[♪ "Blinding Lights" playing]
我一直打电话给你
♪ I've been tryna call ♪
-我独自度日已经够久 -快拿到了
-♪ I've been on my own for long enough ♪ -[rat] Almost got it.
也许你能让我学会如何爱人，也许
♪ Maybe you can show me how to love Maybe ♪
Oh.
我正在经历戒断反应
♪ I'm goin' through withdrawals ♪
你根本不用多费力气
♪ You don't even have to do too much ♪
轻轻一碰就能点燃我的情欲，宝贝
♪ You can turn me on With just a touch, baby ♪
我环顾四周，这罪恶之城冰冷又空虚
♪ I look around and Sin City's cold and empty ♪
附近没有人会批判我
-♪ No one's around to judge me ♪ -[rats] ♪ Oh, oh ♪
没有你，我看什么都不清晰
♪ I can't see clearly when you're gone ♪
我说，这灯光让我睁不开眼
♪ I said, ooh, I'm blinded by the lights ♪
没有你的触碰，我无法入眠
♪ No, I can't sleep Until I feel your touch ♪
我说，我沉溺在这夜色之中
♪ I said, ooh, I'm drowning in the night ♪
在这种时刻，你是我唯一信赖的人
♪ Oh, when I'm like this You're the one I trust ♪
[rats] ♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
-Ah! -[rats clamoring]
我说，这灯光让我睁不开眼
♪ I said, ooh, I'm blinded by the lights ♪
没有你的触碰，我无法入眠
♪ No, I can't sleep Until I feel your touch ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
[grunting, exclaims]
[clamoring]
-去抓鸟 -我抓到鸟了
-Get the bird! Get the bird! -I got the bird.
你有没有看到…
Did you see…
抱歉，声带休息中，不能说话 声带休息中
Sorry! On vocal rest, can't talk. On vocal rest.
斯库特，这里怎么了？
-Scooter, what is going on here? -Hmm?
我是下一个吧？
Am I on next or what?
科米不得不删掉你的表演，猪小姐 他没跟你说吗？
Oh, uh. Kermit had to cut your number, Miss Piggy. Didn't he tell you?
什么？看起来像他有跟我说吗？
What? Does it look like he told me?
你以为我穿这双罗马鞋 是为了足部健康吗？
You think I'm wearing these gladiator sandals for my freaking health?
应该不是
Uh… Probably not.
-[grunts] Kermit! -Whoa!
科米
对，能回来真好
Yep. Good to be back.
很抱歉刚才出了点状况
So sorry about the mishap earlier.
我们还在处理一些小毛病
[stammers] We're still working out a few kinks.
没关系，有病才好玩
Oh, that's all right. I love a kink.
Uh-huh. Hmm.
我只是想说
Well, uh, I just wanted to say
我们真的很荣幸今晚能跟你同台
we're really honored to have you here with us tonight.
你在说笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
能来这里是美梦成真
-Being here is a dream come true. -Ah.
我今晚大可去世上的任何地方
I mean, I could've been anywhere else in the world tonight.
我婉拒了普利策奖
-I… I turned down a Pulitzer prize… -Mmm. Mmm.
让我的脸铸在新的25分硬币上 还有第二次约会，对象是…
…and getting my face on the new quarter, and a second date with… [whispers]
真的吗？
-Really? -Mm-hmm.
-他单身？ -不是
-He's single? -No.
Oh.
但我现在只想待在这里
But this is the only place I want to be right now.
没什么能…
-And nothing could-- -[knocks on door]
开门，青蛙
-[Miss Piggy] Open the door, frog! -[gasps]
-抱歉… -她知道了，老大
-Sorr… -[Scooter] She knows, boss!
好像有人在门外
I think someone's at the door.
-[banging on door] -[grunting]
Uh, ooh, that? [chuckles]
那个？
不，那是…只是剧院太老旧而已
No, no, no, no. That's, uh… That's just an old theater, you know?
这些管线有时候蛮吵的
-Uh, these pipes can be pretty noisy. -[Miss Piggy] Hi-yah!
[exclaims]
他在哪里？
Where is he?
（更衣室）
Wow, the door wasn't even locked.
门根本没上锁
我知道你在这里，青蛙
I know you're here, frog.
猪小姐？
-[Kermit whimpering] -Miss Piggy?
你一定听到腻了，其实我之前就想跟你说
I'm sure you get this all the time, I actually meant to tell you earlier,
你是我的偶像
but you're my idol.
-Aw. -Yeah,
对，我的打扮和风格都是模仿你的
I basically, like, modeled my whole look and style after you.
相信我，我跟我的律师团已经注意到 我们会跟你联系的
Oh, trust me. My attorneys and I have taken notice, and we will be in touch.
Aw. And I'll make sure my attorneys respond… to your attorneys.
我会确保我的律师团回应…你的律师团的
[Kermit whimpers, groans]
你有听到吗？
Did you hear that?
科米说剧院很老旧，管线有点吵
Oh, Kermit said the theater is really old and the pipes are a little noisy.
是吗？科米还说了什么？
Oh, really? What else did Kermit say?
他有提到他删掉我重要的表演了吗？
Did he mention he cut my big number from the show?
什么？不，太扯了
What? No. That-That's crazy.
没有猪小姐的表演 就不叫《大青蛙布偶秀》
There's no Muppet Show without a Miss Piggy number.
一点也没错
-Exactly. -[Carpenter chuckles]
真希望他能亲耳听到
If only he were around to hear that.
门好重
[Kermit, straining] Door's heavy.
真遗憾
I am so sorry.
你不该失去任何一秒的上镜时间 你是传奇人物
You don't deserve to lose one second of screen time. You are an icon.
别说了，你太窝心了，继续
-Oh, stop it. You're too sweet. Go on. -[chuckles]
我从小看你的表演长大 我爸妈从小看你的表演长大
Oh, I mean, I grew up watching you, my parents grew up watching you,
-他们的爸妈从小… -好，见面会结束了
-their parents grew up watching… -Okay! Meet-and-greet over.
要是科米敢现身
-[Kermit groaning] -If Kermit ever shows his face,
你跟他说，我要在这场秀献唱
you let him know. I am going to sing in this show!
-[Kermit whimpers] Help me. -Oh, no! That's right.
-帮帮我 -不，对哦
你还好吗？抱歉
-[Kermit groaning] -Are you okay? Sorry.
我忘了你在底下
I forgot you were down there.
我没事，莎宾娜，我…
-Hey, I'm fine, Sabrina. Yeah, I… -[sighs]
这种事比你想像的更常见
It happens a lot more than you'd think.
斯库特
Uh, Scooter!
你知道流程的，再弄扇门进来吧
You know the drill. Let's get another door in here.
已经在处理了，老大
Already on it, boss.
[chuckles]
其实我见过科米几次
-[snores] -I've actually met Kermit a few times.
他真的非常讨喜
He's actually really lovely.
我见过一大堆名人
-I mean, I've met a ton of celebrities. -[groaning]
很多都是混蛋
A lot of jerks.
-[groaning] -But not Kermit.
但科米不是
-我是大混蛋吗？ -对，但没那么大啦
-Was I a big jerk? -I mean, yes. But not that big.
Mmm? [sighs]
对了，我是玛雅
-Oh, I'm Maya by the way. -Mmm?
[grunts]
[kisses]
Mm-hmm.
欢迎来到布偶实验室，未来的诞生之地
Welcome to Muppet Labs, where the future is being made today.
我是邦森蜜瓜博士 这位是我无畏的助手倒楣鬼
I'm Dr. Bunsen Honeydew, and this is my fearless assistant Beaker.
[screams]
Hmm. [clicks tongue]
今天我们要对抗一种现代流行病：分心
Today we tackle a modern epidemic: distraction.
这年头，一切都在争夺你的目光
-[whimpering] -These days,
everything is competing for your eyeballs.
移动设备、电视，还有我们不看它们时
Mobile devices, televisions and the day-to-day terrors
不断占据我们脑海的日常恐惧
that consume our brains when we aren't looking at the first two.
现在你可以轻松地集中精力
Well, now you can focus effortlessly
只要有我最新的发明“专心汁汁”
thanks to my latest invention, "Focus Pocus."
每只眼睛滴一滴这种精华液
-[whimpers] -One drop of this serum per eye,
你的专注力就会指数级增长
and your attention span will multiply exponentially.
[gasps, meeps]
倒楣鬼，回来，坐在凳子上
[stammers] Beaker, come back, come back. Sit on the stool.
-什么？ -对，很好
-Huh? -That's it. Good. Now,
我要轻轻地把凳子降低
I'm gonna just lower the stool gently.
来吧
-[meeping, breathing heavily] -There, there we go.
小小一滴，我一点都不会痛
A little teeny drop. This won't hurt me at all.
[Beaker whimpering]
好了，没事了
-There we go. There, there, there. -[whimpering]
哎呀，这效果可能有一点太强了
Oh, dear. That might've been just a teensy bit too strong.
-[mutters] -[whimpering]
-[meeping] -Hmm.
我可能没把它稀释得当
Maybe I neglected to dilute it properly.
我看看，我把它写在哪里了？
Now, let's see. Where did I write that down?
[whimpering, gasps]
[sighs]
-[meeping, whimpering] -Oh, this is interesting.
真有意思
这标注了“紧急”
This one's marked urgent.
应该没关系
Hmm. I'm sure that's fine.
[screaming]
倒楣鬼…倒楣鬼，停下来
Oh, Beaker. Beaker. Beaker, stop it. Stop it!
-真令人振奋 -令人振奋
-It's so inspiring. -Inspiring.
我觉得我充满活力
-I feel alive, you know? -Mm-hmm.
身为表演者…
I mean, as a performer…
玛雅？玛雅
Maya? Maya? M-Maya!
斯库特
-[Muppets clamoring] -Scooter,
我妈咪今晚也在观众席
my mommy's in the audience tonight.
我什么时候上台？斯库特
When do I go on? Scooter! Scooter!
我马上就准备好，只要…
-I will be ready as soon as I do my… -[muttering]
哇，你还好吗，科米？
-Oh, wow. Like, are you okay, Kermit? -[exclaims]
还好
[stutters] Yeah.
因为你看起来有点紧绷
'Cause you seem a little wound up.
你的脉轮完全失去平衡了
Like, like your chakras are, like, totally out of whack.
你说得对，我确实有点压力
[grunts] You're right. I guess I am a little stressed.
谢谢你的关心
[chuckles] Thanks for checking in.
好说，因为我能感应气场 而你的气场很糟糕
Oh, for sure. 'Cause you know, like, I can read auras, and yours is, like, bad.
-是吗？ -是的
-It is? -Oh, totally.
我们要吸气…
And we're breathing in… [inhales deeply]
要这么做是吗？
[stammering] Oh, is that what we're doing? Uh… [inhales deeply]
贾妮斯？我能吐气了吗？
[straining] Janice? Can I breathe out yet?
[exhales sharply] Hmm? Janice?
贾妮斯？
Oh. Huh. Actually, that did make me feel a bit better.
其实，我确实觉得好一点了
仿佛情况即将好转
[chuckles] Almost like things are gonna be okay.
为您插播《布偶快讯》
This is a Muppet Newsflash.
曾获艾美奖的喜剧天后玛雅鲁道夫死了
Emmy award-winning comedy icon Maya Rudolph is dead.
什么？
Huh?
我看到那道光，那里有一条灵魂之河
I saw the light, and there was a river of souls.
还有一道火墙
And a… a wall of flames.
我本来在为一个红衣男 准备颁奖典礼开场白
And I was doing award show patter for a man in red.
听起来像天堂，对吧？
-That sounds like heaven. Right? -[whimpers, grunts]
我修正，曾获艾美奖的 喜剧天后玛雅鲁道夫活着
Correction. Emmy award-winning comedy icon Maya Rudolph is alive.
（玛雅鲁道夫死亡）
（玛雅鲁道夫活着）
A thing fell on her and made her be alive again.
有东西掉到她身上，让她复活了
请继续关注更多重磅新闻
Stay tuned for more hard-hitting news.
…琥碧戈柏、安洁莉卡休斯顿 克萝丽丝莉姬曼
…Whoopi Goldberg, Anjelica Huston, Cloris Leachman.
Hmm. Show's not half bad.
这场秀不算糟
对，是糟透了
Yeah, it's all bad.
[laughing]
[♪ "Islands in the Stream" playing]
♪ La, la La, la ♪
宝贝，当我遇见你，我心从未如此平静
♪ Baby, when I met you There was peace unknown ♪
我细心周到地追求你
♪ I set out to get you With a fine tooth comb ♪
我的心变得温柔
♪ I was soft inside ♪
美好之事正在发生
-♪ There was something going on ♪ -[singers] ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ La, la ♪
你对我有无法解释的影响
[both] ♪ You do something to me That I can't explain ♪
紧紧抱着我，我就不会感到痛苦
♪ Hold me closer and I feel no pain ♪
我心脏的每次跳动
♪ Every beat of my heart ♪
都是我们的爱在萌芽
-♪ We got something going on ♪ -[singers] ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ La, la ♪
溪流中的岛屿
♪ Islands in the stream ♪
就是我们的写照
♪ That is what we are ♪
没人能介入，我们的爱怎会有错？
♪ No one in between How can we be wrong? ♪
与我一同扬帆
-♪ Sail away with me ♪ -[Miss Piggy grunting]
航向另一个世界
♪ To another world ♪
-我们互相依赖 -你休想删掉我的戏份
-♪ And we rely on each other, ah ha ♪ -You're not gonna cut me from the show.
水手间的承诺
♪ From one sailor to another, ah ha ♪
[grunting, panting]
若这爱的小船不在，我将无法独活
♪ I can't live without you If this boat was gone ♪
如果没人陪伴
♪ Everything is nothing ♪
一切都是虚无
-♪ If you've got no one ♪ -[pants, screams]
你只会在夜里划行，逐渐看不见真爱
♪ And you just row in the night Slowly losing sight of the real thing ♪
真爱
♪ The real thing ♪
-[vocalizes] -[grunts]
[exclaims]
但我们不会碰上，我们深信不疑
♪ But that won't happen to us And we've got no doubt ♪
此刻你在船上，而我惊慌失措
♪ Now you're in this boat And I am freaking out ♪
这讯息再清晰不过
♪ And the message is clear ♪
今年或许就是真爱降临之年
♪ This could be the year For the real thing ♪
真爱
-♪ The real thing ♪ -♪ La, la ♪
-溪流中的岛屿 -岛屿
-♪ Islands in the stream ♪ -♪ In the stream ♪
-就是我们的写照 -一同扬帆
-♪ That is what we are ♪ -♪ Sail away, sail away ♪
没人能介入
♪ No one in between ♪
我们的爱怎会有错？
-♪ How can we be wrong? ♪ -[grunts]
-与我一同扬帆 -一同扬帆
-♪ Sail away with me ♪ -♪ Sail away ♪
航向另一个世界
♪ To another world ♪
我们互相依赖
-♪ And we rely on each other, ah ha ♪ -♪ Ah ha ♪
天后间的承诺
-♪ From one diva to another, ah ha ♪ -♪ Ah ha ♪
[audience cheering]
-[muttering] -Oh.
你好
-Hi. -Hmm?
我必须说，跟你合唱一直是我的梦想
I just have to say singing a duet with you
-has always been a dream of mine. -Mmm.
现在我做到了，而我还这么年轻
And now I've done it, and I'm still so young.
对，跟我一样，我很年轻，非常年轻
Yes! Just like me! I'm young. Very.
看看我们，两个正值巅峰的年轻新星
Look at us, two young ingenues at the top of their game.
[laughing]
[both laughing]
[sighs]
这代表我们没事了吗？
Well, um… Does this mean we're… we're good then?
你不会控告我剽窃你的造型吧？
You're not gonna try to sue me for stealing your look?
这叫侵犯著作权，亲爱的
It's called copyright infringement, sweetie.
当然不会告你了
-And of course not! -[chuckling] Oh.
真的要由律师团决定
That's really for the lawyers to decide.
[Muppets clamoring]
我正在竭尽所能
[Kermit] I'm trying to do the best I can.
…其中一项表演，我们尽量公平
…one of the acts. We're trying to be fair.
-我们尽量公平对待大家 -我知道
-We're trying to be fair to everybody. -I know. No, I know.
好，大家都别说了
-Okay, everybody, stop! -[gasps]
只剩一项表演的时间了
[sighs] There is only time for one more act.
-什么？ -一项？
-[Muppets mutter] What? -One more?
但是哪一项，老大？
-But which one, boss? -Hmm?
你要怎么选？
How are you gonna choose?
他们怎么这么慢？
-[audience whispering] -What's taking them so long?
[Muppets clamoring]
听着，你们信任我吗？
Look, do you trust me?
我们当然信任你，科米 这家伙可能不信啦
Well, of course we do, Kermit. I mean, maybe not this guy.
我以前吃过亏
I been burned before.
好…给我一分钟，好吗？
[sighs] Okay, uh… [stammers] Give me a minute, okay?
-你要去哪里？等等… -好，借过，抱歉
-Where you going? Wait… -[Kermit] Yeah. Excuse me. I'm sorry.
-他…要做什么？ -科米？
-What… What's he gonna do? -Kermit?
[audience applauds]
大家好，目前为止都还好吗？
Hey there, folks. Uh, how you all doing so far?
Ooh. Um… [chuckles]
我不能说这场秀完全按照计划进行
[stammers] I can't say that the show has gone exactly the way we planned.
洁美李寇蒂斯、蕾吉娜金恩
-Jamie Lee Curtis. Regina King! -[crashes]
重点是，也许我们有点生疏了
Eh, the point is… [stammers] …maybe we're a little rusty.
但我们承诺要为各位献上精彩大秀
But, uh, but we promised to do a great show for you
希望你们至少能享受部分演出
and, uh… [stammers] …I hope that you at least enjoyed some of it.
现在到了尾声
[stammers] Now we're at the end
各位大概都在猜压轴表演是什么
and you're all probably wondering what the final number is.
其实，我本来应该上来
I-In fact, I was supposed to come out here
宣布在后台等候的表演者之一
and announce one of the acts waiting backstage. [chuckles]
但…很抱歉，我不会那么做
But, um… [clears throat] …I'm sorry. Uh, I'm not gonna do that.
[murmuring]
看吧？没人靠得住
-See? Can't trust anyone. -[gasps]
Mmm.
今晚
♪ Tonight ♪
我们将尽情享受真正的美好时光
♪ We're gonna have ourselves A real good time ♪
我充满了活力
♪ I feel alive ♪
我要翻转整个世界
♪ And the world I'll turn it inside out ♪
好耶
Yeah.
我漂浮在狂喜之中
♪ I'm floating around in ecstasy ♪
所以…
[Muppets] ♪ So don't-- ♪
现在别阻止我，别阻止我
♪ Stop me now Don't stop me ♪
因为我们玩得正开心，玩得正开心
♪ 'Cause we're having a good time Having a good time ♪
我是流星，像老虎般跃过天空
♪ I'm a shooting star Leaping through the sky like a tiger ♪
公然违抗地心引力
-♪ Defying the laws of gravity, whoo-hoo ♪ -[meeping]
我是呼啸而过的赛车
♪ I'm a racing car passing by ♪
就像戈黛娃夫人
♪ Like Lady Godiva ♪
我要冲冲冲，因为我完全不想停下来
♪ I'm gonna go, go, go 'Cause I don't wanna stop at all ♪
别阻止我，别阻止我
♪ Don't stop me Don't stop me ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
别阻止我，别阻止我
♪ Don't stop me Don't stop me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
别阻止我，别阻止我
♪ Don't stop me Don't stop ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
别阻止我，别阻止我
♪ Don't stop me Don't stop me ♪
玩得正开心，开心
♪ Have a good time Good time ♪
别阻止，别阻止
Don't stop, don't stop!
现在别阻止我，因为我玩得正开心
♪ Don't stop me now 'Cause I'm having a good time ♪
现在别阻止我
♪ Don't stop me now ♪
因为我玩得正开心，我完全不想停下来
♪ 'Cause I'm having a good time I don't wanna stop at all ♪
[vocalizes]
-[audience cheering] -[chuckles]
太棒了，我们做到了，好耶
That was great! We did it! Yeah!
其实我有点受不了，他们想删我的表演
If I'm being honest, I'm a little insulted they were gonna cut me
却留着这只穿芭蕾舞裙的犰狳
but they kept this armadillo in the tutu in there.
我根本没看过那家伙
Never even seen that guy.
他不是官方角色
That guy's not canon.
我们的时间差不多到了
Well, that's about all the time we have.
但在结束前
But before we go,
让我们以热烈掌声感谢超棒的嘉宾 莎宾娜卡本特
let's give a great big thank you to our incredible guest star, Sabrina Carpenter!
好耶
-[audience cheering] -Yay!
谢谢你，科米
Thank you, Kermit. [chuckles]
你跟我们非常合拍，莎宾娜
Well, you know, uh, you fit right in with us, Sabrina.
-我们身高一样，很有帮助 -说得好
-Well, it helps we're the same height. -[chuckles] Good point!
黛安薇丝特
Dianne Wiest!
Oh. Um… [chuckles] Good night, everybody!
各位晚安
下回《大青蛙布偶秀》见
We'll see you next time on The Muppet Show!
[Muppets chattering]
柔伊莎达娜
Zoe Saldaña! [yelps]
[audience chattering]
我的左臂突然刺痛起来，不知道怎么搞的
Hmm. I got this sharp pain in my left arm. I wonder what that's about.
我只能说，绝对不是鼓掌造成的
I'll tell you this much, it's not from clapping.
-[exclaims, laughs] Ow. -[laughs]
字幕翻译：宋梅君